http://www.humana.org/privacy-policy

Humana People To People
Who We AreAbout usHistoryOur PartnersFinancial InformationFrequently Asked QuestionsWhat We DoSustainable Agriculture and EnvironmentCommunity DevelopmentHealthEducationCollection and Sales of Second-hand ClothesStories from our workTCE - Accomplishments in Fighting HIV and AIDSWhere We WorkAfricaAmericasAsiaEuropeMoreNewsPublicationsBlogPodcastContact us
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Who We Are
About usHistoryOur partnersFinancial informationFrequently asked questions
What We Do
Sustainable Agriculture and EnvironmentCommunity DevelopmentHealthEducationCollection and Sales of Second-hand ClothesStories from our workTCE - Accomplishments in Fighting HIV and AIDS
NewsBlogPodcastPublicationsContact us
2020 © Humana People To People. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions
